Politics is war.
All the Way is a drama, history, tv movie film directed by Jay Roach.
Johnson's amazing 11-month journey from taking office after JFK's assassination, through the fight to pass the 1964 Civil Rights Act and his own
presidential campaign, culminating on the night LBJ is actually elected to the office – no longer the 'accidental President.'
Lyndon B. Johnson, played by Bryan Cranston.
Martin Luther King, Jr., played by Anthony Mackie.
Lady Bird Johnson, played by Melissa Leo.
Sen. Richard Russell, played by Frank Langella.
Hubert Humphrey, played by Bradley Whitford.
J. Edgar Hoover, played by Stephen Root.
All the Way is a 2016 American biographical drama television film
based on events during the presidency of Lyndon B.
Directed by Jay Roach and adapted by Robert Schenkkan from his 2012 play All the Way, the film stars Bryan Cranston, who reprises his role as Johnson from the play's 2014 Broadway
production, opposite Melissa Leo as First Lady Lady Bird Johnson; Anthony Mackie as Civil Rights Movement leader Martin Luther King Jr.; and Frank Langella as U.S.
Senator Richard Russell Jr.
from Georgia.
The film was broadcast on HBO on Saturday, May 21, 2016.
The film has received positive reviews, with praise for Cranston's performance.
It has been nominated for a Television Critics Association Award for Outstanding Achievement in Movies, Miniseries and
Specials, with Cranston also nominated for Individual Achievement in Drama for his work on the film.
It was nominated for eight Primetime Emmy Awards, including Outstanding
Television Movie as well as acting nominations for Cranston and Leo.
The film explores themes of usa president, politics,
biography, historical drama, 1960s.
The tone is emotional.